<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Life With the A&#39;baums</title>
    <description>We hope that you will be encouraged (or at least amused...) as we try to keep it real around here. We &quot;A&#39;baums&quot; are a party of four living down yonder (ahem, the South...) who are just trying to live our lives for Jesus. We hope that you can see Him here and that you find Him in the midst of your own &quot;real life.&quot;</description>
    <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:04:53 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:04:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>catching up with the a&#39;baums</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Aaron and I are coming up on our FIFTH wedding anniversary! Five years! And whether you’re a new friend or knew us even before we said, “I do,” here’s a little read to catch you up on what’s been going on with the A’baums.</p>

<p>We were married in my hometown in Spring 2011. Aaron accepted a job in Virginia after graduating the previous December; after our wedding he whisked me away in our carriage (also known as Ellie May, my awesome Ford Explorer) and we started our life together. It was good and it was very tough. We were a long way from any family and the only “home” I’d ever known. But we had each other and we were sure God had a plan. <strong>And He did.</strong></p>

<p>It was hard. We prayed for me a job. We prayed for an open door to move closer to home. And then… I was offered a job at our church in Children’s Ministry. The day that I signed my papers, Aaron’s boss called and said that we could transfer to back to Georgia within the next few months. We felt called to stay in Virginia, and I’m glad we did.</p>

<p>Though I was employed at our church, we <strong>both</strong> poured our hearts and time into ministry. We learned a lot, we grew a lot, and we built relationships with those around us. We bought a car together. Later we bought our first house. And eventually we got pregnant with Baby Baum #1 (Asher!) It was a joyful season in our lives.</p>

<p>We loved our life in Virginia, but after we were there for about three years we felt a tug in our hearts to move closer to “home.” We prayed for several months about it, and then, in God’s <em>awesome</em> timing, a door was opened for us to move back to Georgia. Aaron had an incredible job offer and within three weeks, Asher turned one, we packed up our house, moved into a little apartment, and Aaron started his job. We were filled with excitement and expectation for the days ahead.</p>

<p>While Aaron loved (and still does) his job, we had some curveballs thrown our way in our new town. One week to the day of our big move we had to rush Asher to the ER for an allergic reaction. <strong>It was scary.</strong> Within the next few weeks it was confirmed that he was allergic to peanuts and, for the time being, we were to avoid all tree nuts as well. We delved into learning more about his diagnosis and the world of food allergies. It was a lifestyle change for us as we did our research and all that we could to keep him safe and healthy. We prayed. <strong>A LOT.</strong></p>

<p>Within the next month, we found out that we were pregnant with Baby Baum #2 (Addy!) It was exciting but with everything else going on (pregnancy hormones, Asher’s allergy, still learning a new town) I had a <em>LOT</em> of anxiety. Again, life was very good, but it was very <em>HARD</em>. And again, we prayed - a lot! Thankfully we had a few friends in our area and were able to see my family much more often, which was so helpful during this time.</p>

<p>At our twenty-week ultrasound for Addy we were told that something looked “abnormal.” From there we went through a series of testing and specialist visits throughout the remainder of the pregnancy. We made it through the summer in our teeny little apartment and finally found a house to rent with more room and <em>much</em> closer to Aaron’s work. Fast-forward to her due date and Addy was born healthy and beautiful!</p>

<p>Since moving back to Georgia, I have had the opportunity to be a stay-at-home-mama. At first, I wasn’t sure how this would go. I was thankful we were able to do it, but I didn’t know how I would adjust. Truth be told, I’m still adjusting and as a family we’re still figuring out our place in this community and season of our lives. Life right now is really, really good. But some days can still seem pretty hard.</p>

<p>I do realize our “hard” is a dream for some people. We don’t take our blessings lightly and know that God has answered so many prayers to provide for and to protect our family. But no matter what the seasons in life are like or even what happens day to day, I’m so thankful to serve an awesome God who never changes. He is there to hold our hand and help us through whatever we may face (Isaiah 41:13.)</p>

<p>So that brings us to where we are now. I’m super thankful to do life with Aaron. We’ve both changed a lot in the last five years, but life does that to ya. When it comes down to it, we are better together. We’re also better for the people that are in our lives. Some people have been with us all along. Some we’ve met along the way. And some are still journeying with us. Regardless of whether we were friends for a season or remain friends today, we’re thankful for what each relationship has taught us and for some really great memories made. We’re looking forward doing life together and many more sweet memories to come.</p>

<p>Keepin’ it real and stuff,</p>

<p>Alyssa</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/03/01/catching-up/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/03/01/catching-up/index.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>alyssa</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>asherisms, part 1</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>As a toddler, Asher says many things that are very unique. Being around him, we’ve come up a little mini translation guide for speaking in <em>Asher</em>. Some of his words are clear, while others are more of a stretch.</p>

<p>This is the first of many, and I hope you enjoy every single one.</p>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th>English</th>
      <th>Asherism</th>
      <th>Example</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td>Tooter</td>
      <td>Toodeler</td>
      <td>(<em>points to Addy</em>) Toodeler!</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Walk</td>
      <td>Run</td>
      <td><strong>Me</strong>: Do you want to go for a walk?<br /><strong>Asher</strong>: Run?</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Like</td>
      <td>Wike</td>
      <td>I wike it!</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Please</td>
      <td>Pease</td>
      <td>Thomas? Watch? I want. Pease.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Yogurt</td>
      <td>Gurt</td>
      <td>Gurt? I want. Pease.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Mayonnaise</td>
      <td>Gurt</td>
      <td>(<em>points to toy mayo bottle</em>) Gurt!</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Addy</td>
      <td>Maddy</td>
      <td>Maddy! Where are you?</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Numbers (13-19)</td>
      <td>Wonteen</td>
      <td>Eleven, twelve, wonteen, wonteen, twenty!</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Airplane</td>
      <td>Pane</td>
      <td>(<em>points up</em>) Pane!</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Lightning McQueen</td>
      <td>Queen</td>
      <td>Cars! Queen! Fast!</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Percy</td>
      <td>Woicey</td>
      <td>Thomas and Woicey, Thomas and Friends</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Frozen</td>
      <td>Frin-in</td>
      <td>Owaf, Sven, Elsa, Anna, Frin-in</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<p>Asher adds new words daily, so check back for more soon!</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 11:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/27/asherisms-part-1/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/27/asherisms-part-1/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>asherisms</category>
        
        
        <category>aaron</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>swagger wagon</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Real life is… when you finally buy that minivan that you promised yourself you’d never drive.</p>

<p>Dear thirteen-year old Alyssa, you were wrong. Minivans aren’t so bad. There will come a day in your life where practicality beats out glimmer and glamour (much like those black yoga pants you will wear pretty much every day.) Those babies you daydreamed of having with your Prince Charming? What did you think you were doing to haul them around in, your hot pink Jeep Wrangler?</p>

<p>Listen to me, darling, it has everything you never dreamed of and more. It has holders for every water bottle and sippy cup and container of Wet Wipes you could ever possibly need. It has space for the kids, your ginormous diaper bag, and everyone’s Christmas presents as you make the trek home for the holidays. It also has that that “mommy space” (okay, just really comfy front seat) you’ll need when the house is messy and loud and you leave your Prince inside to the ~~wolves~~ kids to retreat for ~~a half hour~~ ten minutes of solitude in the garage. It has features that you can’t really imagine yet how good they’ll be- like the DVD player for your toddler to watch Toy Story on repeat, a rearview camera so you don’t hit any ~~people~~ mailboxes, and not just automatic side doors but backdoor as well, so you don’t drop any ~~children~~ bags in the parking lot. As your buddy Rhea will say to you (yes, you are still great friends after all of these years), just embrace it! You’ll balk a little at first, but once your SIL sings the praises of her mini you’ll begin to give in little by little. Your Prince will be pretty excited about it and there’s just something about him on daddy duty that makes him go up a couple more notches on the hott-ness scale.</p>

<p>I know… other vehicles will have nice features, too. But this is practical for your life in this season. And it fits in your garage. The point is, things change. Times change. Priorities change. And you’ll change, too. But whatever, thirteen-year old Alyssa. Go back to singing to your Grease soundtrack (wait, you’ll still do that over a decade later…) and doing your homework. Don’t worry your pretty little bangs about such things. Time will tell soon enough.</p>

<p>In the meantime, we A’baums will be cruising down I-75 in our swagger wagon - jamming to the best of Disney, riding ~~dirty~~ with dirty diapers (in the handy trash bag holder our mini so conveniently has), and living the wild life in the far right lane.</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 21:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/23/swagger-wagon/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/23/swagger-wagon/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>reallifeis</category>
        
        <category>parentingstuff</category>
        
        
        <category>alyssa</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>rest for your soul</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>What’s that burden you’re carrying? Is it a private one? One that you feel like the whole world knows?</p>

<p>What’s that prayer that you whisper constantly through the day? The one you’ve woken up and prayed for countless times. Over and over.</p>

<p>What’s that thing that’s wearing you down? That relationship? That schedule? Those bills?</p>

<p>That thing that’s been on your mind since you saw that headline come across your newsfeed. That hope in your heart since you saw those test results. That fear that you’ve tried to squelch ever since that scary night in the ER.</p>

<p>I don’t have any easy fixes or 10 ways to make it better. We surely don’t have it all together over here. BUT, Jesus does say the same thing to you and to me.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“<strong>Come to me, all you who are weary and burdened, and I will give you rest.</strong> Take my yoke upon you and learn from me, for I am gentle and humble in heart, and you will find rest for your souls. <strong>For my yoke is easy and my burden is light.</strong>” <cite>Matthew 11:28-30 (NIV, emphasis added)</cite></p>
</blockquote>

<p>Whatever that prayer, whatever that burden, give it over to Him. Daily. Hourly if needed.</p>

<p>And in Him, find rest.</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 22:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/16/rest-for-you-soul/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/16/rest-for-you-soul/index.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>alyssa</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Of Jobs and Men</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Work life balance isn’t always the easiest thing to achieve. You want to do everything you can to provide for the people you love.</p>

<p>With a second child now, my time is split even more than it was before. Balancing between work and family only gets harder as time goes on.</p>

<p>I am very blessed to work in the technology industry. Technology jobs are leading the path for fathers to be able to more easily balance their time, whether it is from working from home or having flexible work hours. At my previous job, I had the option to work from home full time, and I cherish all of the moments I spent with Asher during his first year. Of course, working from home didn’t mean that I spent all day every day with my family - it meant that I didn’t have a commute in the morning and evening and that I could spend time getting snuggles during work breaks instead of hanging out at the water cooler.</p>

<p>I can occasionally work from home these days, but it is usually limited to when we have a doctor’s appointment. That’s alright though - it is much harder to work from home with two kids than it was with one baby. I am able to take advantage of flexible hours at work though. This lets me spend every morning playing with Asher and every evening playing with Addy.</p>

<p>It’s such a fun routine and it brings me so much joy in the morning to hear Asher calling out “oh daddy, where are you?”, knowing that he is genuinely excited to get up and play with me.</p>

<p>This phase won’t last forever and we’ll find new ways to spend time together, but as for now, I wouldn’t trade my 7-9am for anything (except for some extra sleep occasionally - after all, I am a parent of a 4 month old as well.)</p>

<p>Sometimes, you just need to find the extra margin and appreciate the precious moments you get. They are far beyond worth it, especially since you never get them back.</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 16:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/15/of-jobs-and-men/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/15/of-jobs-and-men/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>reallifeis</category>
        
        <category>dadlife</category>
        
        <category>worklifebalance</category>
        
        
        <category>aaron</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>let me Google that for you</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Real life is… when you Google “toddler tantrums” but you’re not seeing anything that you haven’t already tried. (Ignoring it, not ignoring it, trying to figure out if he is still tired or hungry or probably all of it or maybe none of it, and  “hey, do you want to go watch Thomas?”)</p>

<p>So you take a deep breath and pray. And in your head you know you’re not the only mama dealing with this right now, but it kind of feels that way.</p>

<p>Anyways, thanks Lysa TerKeurst for the reminder that, “bad moments don’t make bad mamas.” And thank you, Jesus, for patience (and for Thomas the train.)</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 20:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/09/let-me-google-that-for-you/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/09/let-me-google-that-for-you/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>reallifeis</category>
        
        <category>parentingstuff</category>
        
        <category>toddlerstuff</category>
        
        
        <category>alyssa</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>baby toots</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Asher called Addy a “toodeler”.</p>

<p>To be fair, Addy does have a lot of gas. And it <strong>smells. so. bad.</strong></p>

<p>But he really is very sweet to her and likes snuggling up to her.</p>

<p>It’s some good <em>#siblinglove</em>.</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 16:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/baby-toots/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/baby-toots/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>siblinglove</category>
        
        <category>toddlerlife</category>
        
        <category>asherisms</category>
        
        <category>smh</category>
        
        
        <category>aaron</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Life</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey, y’all! Welcome to <em>real life with the a’baums</em>! Here, we’re just trying to keep it real. And as you know, sometimes <em>real life</em> gets sticky… with baby drool and spilled milk and words that would have been better left unsaid. But sometimes, <em>real life</em> is really sweet… like morning snuggles and silly giggles and his hand holding yours as you whisper nighttime prayers.</p>

<p>But you probably already know that, right? Because you’re living your own <em>real life</em>, too. Real life with your own real schedules and real responsibilities. Real life with your own messes to tidy, checks to sign, and mouths to feed. Real life with your own struggles and heartaches and loads to bear. Real life with real moments that, on many days, just fly by altogether too quickly.</p>

<p>In that, we have something in common. Though on the outside our lives might seem quite different, we really are more alike than you think. We’re all just trying to live <em>real life</em>, and hope to make it count for something.</p>

<p>So regardless of where you are on your <em>real life</em> journey, we hope you stop by again soon. Together maybe we’ll find that real life, in fact, is really quite beautiful.</p>

<p>Keepin’ it real and stuff,</p>

<p>Alyssa</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/real-life/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/real-life/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>reallifeis</category>
        
        
        <category>alyssa</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
