<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Life With the A&#39;baums</title>
    <description>We hope that you will be encouraged (or at least amused...) as we try to keep it real around here. We &quot;A&#39;baums&quot; are a party of four living down yonder (ahem, the South...) who are just trying to live our lives for Jesus. We hope that you can see Him here and that you find Him in the midst of your own &quot;real life.&quot;</description>
    <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 20:20:26 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 20:20:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>let me Google that for you</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Real life is… when you Google “toddler tantrums” but you’re not seeing anything that you haven’t already tried. (Ignoring it, not ignoring it, trying to figure out if he is still tired or hungry or probably all of it or maybe none of it, and  “hey, do you want to go watch Thomas?”)</p>

<p>So you take a deep breath and pray. And in your head you know you’re not the only mama dealing with this right now, but it kind of feels that way.</p>

<p>Anyways, thanks Lysa TerKeurst for the reminder that, “bad moments don’t make bad mamas.” And thank you, Jesus, for patience (and for Thomas the train.)</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 20:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/09/let-me-google-that-for-you/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/09/let-me-google-that-for-you/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>reallifeis</category>
        
        <category>parentingstuff</category>
        
        <category>toddlerstuff</category>
        
        
        <category>alyssa</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>baby toots</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Asher called Addy a “toodeler”.</p>

<p>To be fair, Addy does have a lot of gas. And it <strong>smells. so. bad.</strong></p>

<p>But he really is very sweet to her and likes snuggling up to her.</p>

<p>It’s some good <em>#siblinglove</em>.</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 16:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/baby-toots/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/baby-toots/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>siblinglove</category>
        
        <category>toddlerlife</category>
        
        <category>asherisms</category>
        
        <category>smh</category>
        
        
        <category>aaron</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Life</title>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey, y’all! Welcome to <em>real life with the a’baums</em>! Here, we’re just trying to keep it real. And as you know, sometimes <em>real life</em> gets sticky… with baby drool and spilled milk and words that would have been better left unsaid. But sometimes, <em>real life</em> is really sweet… like morning snuggles and silly giggles and his hand holding yours as you whisper nighttime prayers.</p>

<p>But you probably already know that, right? Because you’re living your own <em>real life</em>, too. Real life with your own real schedules and real responsibilities. Real life with your own messes to tidy, checks to sign, and mouths to feed. Real life with your own struggles and heartaches and loads to bear. Real life with real moments that, on many days, just fly by altogether too quickly.</p>

<p>In that, we have something in common. Though on the outside our lives might seem quite different, we really are more alike than you think. We’re all just trying to live <em>real life</em>, and hope to make it count for something.</p>

<p>So regardless of where you are on your <em>real life</em> journey, we hope you stop by again soon. Together maybe we’ll find that real life, in fact, is really quite beautiful.</p>

<p>Keepin’ it real and stuff,</p>

<p>Alyssa</p>
]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/real-life/index.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://reallifewiththeabaums.com/2016/02/07/real-life/index.html</guid>
        
        <category>reallifeis</category>
        
        
        <category>alyssa</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
